Guide to the Department of Manuscripts and Archives, Yale University, Reference Service Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Public Services records, 2005-2012; Accession 2012-A-098
  - Aeon Call Slips: All Collections. Late-use, filed chronologically, Circa 1/2012-4/2012 (Box 8, Folder 135)
  - Aeon Call Slips: All Collections. Late-use, filed chronologically, Circa 4/2012 (cont.)-6/2012 (Box 9)
  - Tripart Call Slips: MS 1-1975, 2011-2012 (Box 10)
  - Tripart Call Slips: RU 1-1099; Publications Y-Yz, Dissertations, and Reference; Microformat, HM 4-277, Microfiche, 2011-2012 (Box 11)
  - Yale Photo & Design Receipts, September 2005-March 2012 (Box 12, Folder 136)
  - Yale Broadcast & Media Receipts, July 2005-August 2007 (Box 12, Folder 137)
  - Yale Broadcast & Media Receipts, August 2007-April 2012 (Box 12, Folder 138)
- Public Services records, 2010-2011; Accession 2013-A-008
  - Call slips - manuscripts (MS 1-MS 1563), 2010-2011 (Box 1)
  - Call slips - manuscripts (MS 1564-MS 1975), archives, publications, microformat, 2010-2011 (Box 2)
- Public Services records, 2012; Accession 2013-A-030
  - Reprographics Order Forms A-B, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Reprographics Order Forms C-D, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Reprographics Order Forms E-F, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Reprographics Order Forms G-HA, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Reprographics Order Forms HE-J, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Reprographics Order Forms K-L, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Reprographics Order Forms M, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Reprographics Order Forms N-O, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Reprographics Order Forms P-R, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Reprographics Order Forms S, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Reprographics Order Forms T-V, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Reprographics Order Forms W-Z, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Applications to Examine A-C, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Applications to Examine D-K, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Applications to Examine L-R, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Applications to Examine S-Z, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Reference Correspondence A-AI, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Reference Correspondence AJ-AL, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Reference Correspondence AM-AN, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Reference Correspondence AO-AZ, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Reference Correspondence B-BAZ, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Reference Correspondence BE, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Reference Correspondence BI-BL, 2012 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Reference Correspondence BO, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Reference Correspondence BR, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Reference Correspondence BU-BY, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Reference Correspondence C-CAP, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Reference Correspondence CAR-CAW, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Reference Correspondence CH, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Reference Correspondence CI-CL, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Reference Correspondence CO-COM, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Reference Correspondence CON-COX, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Reference Correspondence CR-CU, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Reference Correspondence DA, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Reference Correspondence DE-DH, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Reference Correspondence DI-DO, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Reference Correspondence DR-DY, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Reference Correspondence E-ENG, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Reference Correspondence ENT-EW, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Reference Correspondence F-FE, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Reference Correspondence FI-FOG, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Reference Correspondence FOL-FY, 2012 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Reference Correspondence GA, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Reference Correspondence GE-GI, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Reference Correspondence GL-GO, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Reference Correspondence GP-GRE, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Reference Correspondence GRI-GU, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Reference Correspondence H-HAN, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Reference Correspondence HAG-HAY, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Reference Correspondence HE, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Reference Correspondence HI, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Reference Correspondence HOO-HOT, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Reference Correspondence HOU-HY, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Reference Correspondence I, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Reference Correspondence I.L.L, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Reference Correspondence J-JE, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Reference Correspondence JO-JU, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Reference Correspondence K-KE, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Reference Correspondence KH-KL, 2012 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Reference Correspondence KN-KW, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Reference Correspondence LA, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Reference Correspondence LE-LEW, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Reference Correspondence LI-LIV, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Reference Correspondence LL-LY, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Reference Correspondence M-MAO, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Reference Correspondence MAR-MAY, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Reference Correspondence Mc, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Reference Correspondence ME-MEY, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Reference Correspondence MEZ-MI, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Reference Correspondence ML-MO, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Reference Correspondence MU-MY, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Reference Correspondence N-NG, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Reference Correspondence NI-NY, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Reference Correspondence O-OP, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Reference Correspondence OR-PA, 2012 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Reference Correspondence PE-PH, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Reference Correspondence PI-POZ, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Reference Correspondence PR-PU, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Reference Correspondence Q-RE, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Reference Correspondence RH-RI, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Reference Correspondence RO-ROH, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Reference Correspondence ROM-ROY, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Reference Correspondence RU-RY, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Reference Correspondence SA, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Reference Correspondence SC, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Reference Correspondence SE-SH, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - Reference Correspondence SI-SKE, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - Reference Correspondence SKI-SMY, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - Reference Correspondence SN-SR, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - Reference Correspondence ST-STE, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - Reference Correspondence STI-SZ, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Reference Correspondence T-TH, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - Reference Correspondence TI-TY, 2012 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - Reference Correspondence U-V, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 94)
  - Reference Correspondence W-WAL, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 95)
  - Reference Correspondence WAN-WAT, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 96)
  - Reference Correspondence WE-WH, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 97)
  - Reference Correspondence WI, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 98)
  - Reference Correspondence WO-WY, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 99)
  - Reference Correspondence X-Z, 2012 (Box 6, Folder 100)
- Public Services records, 2013; Accession 2014-A-005
  Restricted to Office of Origin only.
  - Reference correspondence
    - A-ALD, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ALE-ARM, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ARN-AZ, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - B-BAI, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - BAL-BAU, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - BAT-BEN, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - BER-BLU, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - BO-BRI, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - BRO-BUD, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - BUN-BYR, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - CAE-CAR, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - CAS-CHA, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - CHE-CLI, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - COA-COO, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - COP-CUM, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - CUN-DAN, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - DAR-DEM, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - DEN-DOA, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - DOB-DRI, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - DUA-DYK, 2013 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - EAL-EZ, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - FAL-FAZ, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - FIT-FRO, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - FRY-GAO, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - GAR-GEO, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - GER-GOL, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - GOM-GRE, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - GRI, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - GRO-GRU, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - GUA-HAK, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - HAL-HAN, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - HAR, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - HAS-HEN, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - HER-HIN, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - HIR-HON, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - HOO-HLI, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - HUD-HUG, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - HUL-IVE, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - I.L.L (A-MCY), 2013 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - I.L.L (MNU-ZYU), 2013 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - J-JOHNS, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - JOHNST-JU, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - KAC-KIR, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - KLA-KWO, 2013 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - L-LAZ, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - LED-LFU, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - LEV-LI, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - LIB-LOC, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - LOE-LYS, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - M-MAO, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - MARA-MART, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - MAS-McC, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - McD-MEI, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - MEL-MIL, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - MIN-MOO, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - MOR-MUN, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - MUR-MZ, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - NAC-NEW, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - NG-NUN, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - OAK-OLS, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - OPP-PAL, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - PAN-PEA, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - PED-PFL, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - PHA-POT, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - POW-QUI, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - RAB-RED, 2013 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - REE-RIB, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - RIC-ROB, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - ROC-ROT, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - ROZ-RYA, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - SAA-SCA, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 71)
    - SCHA-SCHW, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 72)
    - SCI-SHI, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 73)
    - SID-SIN, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 74)
    - SIR-SMY, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 75)
    - SNE-SPI, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 76)
    - SPR-STR, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 77)
    - STU-SYN, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 78)
    - TAB-TER, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 79)
    - TES-TRA, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 80)
    - TRE-TYL, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 81)
    - ULL-VIB, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 82)
    - VIT-WAR, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 83)
    - WAS-WES, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 84)
    - WET-WIE, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 85)
    - WIL-WRI, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 85A)
    - YAG-YUR, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 86)
    - Z, 2013 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Photography agreements
    - ACH-EYE, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - FAH-LYN, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - LAN-RUT, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - S-Z, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - Reprographics order forms
    - A-B, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - C-D, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - E-G, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - H-K, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - L-MAO, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - MAR-MUT, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - N-PEL, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - PEP-RIC, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - RID-SMI, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - SOL-TOU, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - TRE-Z, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Applications to examine
    - A-C, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 103)
    - D-K, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 104)
    - L-R, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 105)
    - S-Z, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Broadcast & Media Invoices 3567-4597, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Photo & Design Invoices 9775-11547, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Loan Forms, 2013 (Box 5, Folder 109)
- Public Services records, 1985-2014; 2013-2014; Accession 2015-A-017
  - Correspondence
    - A-Ald, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Ale-Arf, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Arm-Az, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - B-Bar, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Bas-Ben, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Bep-Bi, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Bla-Bow, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Boy-Bro, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Bru-Bz, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Cab-Cav, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Cer-Chr, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Cle-Col, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Con-Cor, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Cot-Cus, 2013-2014 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - D-Dem, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Den-Dow, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Don-Dym, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - E-Ext, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - F-Fis, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Fit-Fus, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Gab-Git, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Gla-Gon, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Gra-Gut, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Hac-Haz, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Hea-Hli, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Ho-Hyl, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - ILL, 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Iam-Johns, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Joi-Kel, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Kem-Koz, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Kra-Kut, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Lab-Laz, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Le-Lev, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Lew-Lin, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Lip-Lyo, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Mac-Mao, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Mara-Marx, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Mas-Mcc, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Mcd-Mcn, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Mea-Mid, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Mil-Mont, 2013-2014 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Moo-Mul, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Mun-Myl, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - N-New, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Ney-Nun, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Obe-Owe, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Pac-Pet, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Phe-Pos, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Pot-Rav, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Ray-Rib, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Ric-Roq, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Ros-Rud, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Ruf-Sam, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - San-Sch, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Scho-Sco, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Sel-Sin, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Sir-Son, 2013-2014 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Sor-Sti, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Sto-Sz, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Tad-Th, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Tic-Tut, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Uba-Von, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Wah-War, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Was-Wes, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Wha-Wil, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Wir-Yu, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - X-Z, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Photo Agreements
    - A-C, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - D-G, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - H-L, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - M-Q, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - R-S, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - T-Z, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Reprographic Orders
    - Abo-Bry, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Bun-Car, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Dai-Ful, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Gal-Huf, 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Iko-Liv, 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Loc- Mur, 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Nak-Ree, 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Ric-Slt, 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Tag-Wil, 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Wom-Zor, 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Application to Examine
    - A-K, 2013-2014 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - L-Z, 2013-2014 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Permission Forms, 2004-2006 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Completed Loan Forms
    - Aeon, 2013-2014 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Selected from Backlog, Materials' Return Verified 07/2014, 1985-2011 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Materials' Return Previously Verified
      - 2002-2004 (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - 2005-2008 (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - 2009-2013 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Public Services records, 1980-2001; Accession 2015-A-023
  - Research requests, 1980-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Research requests, order forms, applications to examine, 1989-1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Order forms, applications to examine
    - 1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 1999 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 2000 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 2001 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Reference requests, 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Office or origin requests (completed), 1997-2000 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Public Services records, 2007-2015; Accession 2016-A-003
  - Reference correspondence
    - A-ALD, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ALG-AVE, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - B-BAR, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - BAT-BEN, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - BER-BIV, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - BLA-BOW, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - BOY-BRON, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - BROO-BUG, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - BUJ-BYR, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - C-CAR, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - CAS-CHOI, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - CIO-COLO, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - COLT-COPE, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - COPP-CZ, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - D-DEM, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - DEN-DON, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - DOU-DY, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - E, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - F-FIS, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - FIT-FU, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - G-GH, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - GIA-GIN, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - GIV-GEN, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - GR-GU, 2014-2015 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - H-HAN, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - HAR-HJ, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - HO-HOU, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - HOV-HY, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - I-IS, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Interlibrary Loan (All), 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - J-JOHNSON, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - JOHNSTON-JU, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - K-KEL, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - KEM-KIT, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - KL-KUP, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - KR-KUS, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - L-LED, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - LEE-LEN, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - LEP-LIN, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - LIP-LY, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - MAC-MAN, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - MAR-MAY, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Mc, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - ME-MIC, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - MIL-MON, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - MOO-MZ, 2014-2015 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - N-NE, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - NI-NU, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - O, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - P-PEA, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - PEI-PF, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - PH-PU, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Q-REA, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - REB-RIC, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - RIG-ROO, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - ROS-RY, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - S-SA, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - SC, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - SE-SHAP, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - SHAR-SIN, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - SIR-SON, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - SOR-STEP, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - STEV-SZ, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - T-TAR, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - TAY-TH, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - TI-TY, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - U-V, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - W-WAR, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - WAS-WE, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - WH-WIL, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - WIN-WY, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - X-Z, 2014-2015 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Photography Agreements All, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Reprographics orders
    - A-B, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - C-D, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - E-G, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - H-I, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - J-K, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - L-M, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - N-P, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - R, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - S, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - T-Z, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Completed Loan Agreements, 2014-2015 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Vendor Services, Various, 2007-2015 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Photo Design Invoices, 2012-2015 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Public Services records, 2009-2016; Accession 2017-A-008
  - Reference Correspondence
    - A-ALD, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ALE-ANG, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - ANS-AZ, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - BAA-BAR, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - BAS-BEN, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - BER-BJ, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - BLA-BOW, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - BOX-BRI, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - BRO, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - BRU-BY, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - CAC-CAR, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - CAS-CH, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - CI-CON, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - COR-CZ, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - DA-DEM, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - DES-DOR, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - DOW-DY, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - E, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - FA-FI, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - FR-FU, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - GA-GE, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - GI-GO, 2015-2016 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - GR-GY, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - HAA-HAM, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - HAN-HAZ, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - HE-HI, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - HO, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - HS-HU, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - I, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - ILL, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - JA-JOI, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - JON-JU, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - KA-KEL, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - KEM-KI, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - KL-KO, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - KR-KU, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - LA-LEM, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - LER-LIN, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - LIP-LY, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - MAC-MAN, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - MAR-MAZ, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - MC, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - ME-MON, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - MOO-MY, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - NA-NE, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - NG-NY, 2015-2016 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - O, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - PA, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - PE, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - PH-PL, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - PO-PU, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Q, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - RA-RE, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - RI-ROB, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - ROC-RY, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - SA, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - SC, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - SE-SIN, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - SIP-SN, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - SO-STI, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - STO-SZ, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - TA-TH, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - TI-TY, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - U-V, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - WA, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - WE, 2015-2016 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - WH-WIL, 2015-2016 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - WIN-WY, 2015-2016 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - X-Z, 2015-2016 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Access Agreements; MS 1659, MS 1090, 2015-2016 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Access Agreements; MS 1090 (2009), MS 318 (2012), 2009-2012 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Reprographics Orders
    - A-B, 2015-2016 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - C-D, 2015-2016 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - E-G, 2015-2016 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - H-J, 2015-2016 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - K-L, 2015-2016 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - M-O, 2015-2016 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - P-R, 2015-2016 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - S-T, 2015-2016 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - U-Z, 2015-2016 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Loan Documentation, 2015-2016 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Vendor Services, Various, 2015-2016 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Public Services records, 2016-2017; Accession 2018-A-007
  - Reference Correspondence
    - A-ALD, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - ALE-ANN, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - APP-AZ, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - BA-BANC, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - BAND-BAR, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - BAS-BEN, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 6)